看骚淫女的性交片网：448𝟖𝟒𝟨𝟿.com
After Porn Ends 2 is a documentary film directed by Bryce Wagoner.
After Porn Ends 2 picks up where its predecessor left off and not only turns back the clock to meet the oldest living stars in adult film's
history, but goes in depth with some of Its most current retirees and juxtaposes their experiences in a life after porn.
Delving deeper into society's ongoing stigmas of race, misogyny, and the reality
of decreasing opportunities for these former VHS box cover stars.
For some, their careers in adult entertainment is
accepted proudly and without regret.
In fact, it seems to have proven to be the pathway to
their current happiness and inner peace.
For others, however, a career in porn has proven to be a conduit to certain despair as they
struggle to find a way to bury their past and emerge with a new career or calling.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Ginger Lynn.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Lisa Ann.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Janine Lindemulder.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Chasey Lain.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Tabitha Stevens.
Self - Former Porn Star, played by Georgina Spelvin.
After Porn Ends is a 2012 American documentary
film about the pornography industry.
It features interviews with Asia Carrera, Nina Hartley, Mary Carey, Randy West, Richard Pacheco, John
Leslie, Amber Lynn, Seka, Raylene, Bill Margold, Shelley Lubben, Luke Ford and Tiffany Million.
The film explores themes of interview, porn actress,
observational documentary, adult industry workers, porno.
The tone is thought_provoking.